Novi Sad, Serbia

VLADIMIR ASEEV

Mobile: +381 63 814 79 50 telegram: @millerrabin

e-mail: rabinmiller@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I've been working on projects for over 20 years.

I work with WEB Backend + Frontend, voice control systems, swarm intelligence and decision making systems.

To choose a stack, I rely on the tactical advantages of the team.

At the start of the carrier, I created an x86-64 application in assembler.

I'm interested in robotics and human-robot communication systems.

I enjoy working with people and enjoy being a team leader.

My development processes are efficient and consistent.

I know how to launch huge distributed projects on time while keeping the team healthy.

My contacts

linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/millerrabin/

git: https://github.com/MillerRabin

youtube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCA23cbnhVDDtOQmUqowhBGw

telegram: @millerrabin

My Favorite technology stack

AWS, Terraform, NodeJS, Kotlin, Go, Rust, C / C++, esp32, System On Chip, PostgreSQL, Oracle, Cassandra, MongoDB, DynamoDB, MariaDB Pure JS, HTML / CSS, VueJS, React, Svelte, TypeScript

EMPLOYMENT

Director Of Engineering NFTee(Spring 2022)

One of my team's projects is https://speakease.co/

It is a voice-controlled mobile/web application.

Voice-controlled applications necessitate cutting-edge UX design and core architectural research.

We designed and implemented a highly scalable / fault-tolerant architecture based on AWS lambda, which included:

- * Voice authentication / authorization
- * Voice navigation
- * Voice asset management (Bitcoin, Solana, Ethereum, Polygon, Binance, Klaytn, Linea, Stellar, Tron)
- * Multitasking at all levels
- * Tasks and meanings conflict resolution

It also demands a team of developers and designers who are capable of solving difficulties they have never seen before.

- * We delivered on schedule
- * Successfully passed Google's review and deployed to Google Play
- * We passed an Astra Security third-party security audit and received an A+
- * Integrate product with fiat On/Off Ramp

Lead Backend Developer OgtaCore

GameTradeMarket (Autumn 2021 - Winter 2022)

This is an exchange for the sale of game items for cryptocurrency.

I created a backend for it (NodeJS, Amazon Lambda), a trading smart contract and a contract for issuing gaming tokens (Solidity ERC721)

Also it offers search for user items in Google Big Query Ethereum Mainnet and Polygon Mainnet and support for game items in Binance Smart Chain.

System Architect JSC Bars Group

VIMIS (Spring 2020 - Summer 2021)

VIMIS stands for Vertically Integrated Medical Information System, and I had the wonderful pleasure to work as a system architect on it. The system passed the PMI and was recommended for use by the Russian Federation's Ministry of Health.

Voice Interfaces

Thinker Robot (autumn 2017 - spring 2020)

The Intention Network is an innovative way for interacting with your laptop or phone. Intention Network transforms your laptop or phone into an assistant. Simply by chatting with it, you can give it a name and ask it to accomplish something or assign a task.

It will find a means to finish the task, outsource it to another device, and be accountable for its completion.

Laptops will learn how to work with cameras, robots, hubs, routers, and other devices.

Head of Frontend Development

Winline (summer 2014 – autumn 2015)

Development of a software package for the work of 60 sport bookmaking outlets throughout Russia Software for cash registers providing work for cashiers in the outlets, taking, calculating, and paying bets.

Live monitors are used to display essential information to large screens.

Remote control software for monitors from cashiers' workstations.

Management of a five-developer resource group.

Senior Support Engineer

Parallels (summer 2011 - autumn 2013)

Work in the tier 3 support line of Parallels

Deployment of virtual workplace system in the Tax Office of Moscow

Ensuring successful passing through Microsoft SVVP for Parallels Server Bare Metal

Developed a line of products for automation of the error processing procedure for tier 2 support line

Education

Siberian Federal University

M.S.E. in Computer Science, Information Security, January 2007.